<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- 0= NORTH,    1 = SOUTH,      2 = EAST,      3 = WEST,      4 = UP,     5 = DOWN -->
<house>
    <room id="hall">
        <roomName>Hall</roomName>
        <floor>First</floor>
        <desc>The entry hall to the haunted house is dimly lit, bowls of candy sit in the corner. You are able to
make out the features of two doors and a staircase. To the EAST, chairs are lined UP around a dining room
table, to the WEST something metallic enclosed in a glass cabinet catches the candle light. The stairs lead
UP into the darkness.
        </desc>
        <roomExits type="array">
            <exit dir="0"></exit>
            <exit dir="1">study</exit>
            <exit dir="2">diningRoom</exit>
            <exit dir="3">trophyRoom</exit>
            <exit dir="4">upstairsLanding</exit>
            <exit dir="5"></exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomItems type="array">
            <item>Bowl of Candy</item>
        </roomItems>
    </room>
    <room id="trophyRoom">
        <roomName>Trophy Room</roomName>
        <floor>First</floor>
        <desc>Thick glass cabinets line the perimeter of this room, displaying all sorts of oddities: old playing cards,
"magic" wands, antique pistols. Mounted animal heads adorn the high walls, grotesque sneers left on their
faces by a taxidermist with an odd sense of taste. A large grisly bear looms over the room from the far corner.
        </desc>
        <roomExits type="array">
            <exit dir="0"></exit>
            <exit dir="1"></exit>
            <exit dir="2">hall</exit>
            <exit dir="3"></exit>
            <exit dir="4"></exit>
            <exit dir="5"></exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomItems type="array">
        </roomItems>
    </room>
    <room id="diningRoom">
        <roomName>Dining Room</roomName>
        <floor>First</floor>
        <desc>A long table occupies the middle of the room, fully set for a dinner of eight.  Dust covers the fine
dinnerware and glasses.  A single glass at the head of the table, next to a lit candle, stands out with red
lipstick on the rim. When you move it, another identical glass materializes in its place. To the NORTH, the sounds of a
busy kitchen come from a dark room, and to the SOUTH a door opens to the outside.</desc>
        <roomExits type="array">
            <exit dir="0">kitchen</exit>
            <exit dir="1">gardens</exit>
            <exit dir="2"></exit>
            <exit dir="3">hall</exit>
            <exit dir="4"></exit>
            <exit dir="5"></exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomItems type="array">
            <item>Smudged Glass</item>
        </roomItems>
    </room>
    <room id="garden">
        <roomName>Garden</roomName>
        <floor>First</floor>
        <desc>Wilted flowers line broken cobblestone paths through the gardens, casting ominous shadows. Gardener's
tools sit at the base of a withered rose bush, an odd red stain is showing on some of them.  The door to the NORTH leads
back inside.</desc>
        <roomExits type="array">
            <exit dir="0">diningRoom</exit>
            <exit dir="1"></exit>
            <exit dir="2"></exit>
            <exit dir="3"></exit>
            <exit dir="4"></exit>
            <exit dir="5"></exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomItems type="array">
            <item>Bloodied Trowel</item>
        </roomItems>
    </room>
    <room id="kitchen">
        <roomName>Kitchen</roomName>
        <floor>First</floor>
        <desc>Sounds of a bustling kitchen come from this entirely unoccupied room. The stoves are off, the pans are
still.  Behind a curtain you notice poorly hidden speakers where the noises seem to originate from. The SOUTH
door showing a dining room table, and along the EAST wall there is a closed door.</desc>
        <roomExits type="array">
            <exit dir="0"></exit>
            <exit dir="1">diningRoom</exit>
            <exit dir="2">pantry</exit>
            <exit dir="3"></exit>
            <exit dir="4"></exit>
            <exit dir="5"></exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomItems type="array">
            <item>Bluetooth Speaker</item>
        </roomItems>
    </room>
    <room id="pantry">
        <roomName>Pantry</roomName>
        <floor>First</floor>
        <desc>Dusty glass bottles, jars, and cans fill this large pantry. The smell of spices wafts out of several open
glass bottles. Do those jars have eyeballs in them? The only door out is WEST to the kitchen</desc>
        <roomExits type="array">
            <exit dir="0"></exit>
            <exit dir="1"></exit>
            <exit dir="2"></exit>
            <exit dir="3">kitchen</exit>
            <exit dir="4"></exit>
            <exit dir="5"></exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomItems type="array">
            <item>Eyeball Jar</item>
        </roomItems>
    </room>
    <room id="study">
        <roomName>Study</roomName>
        <floor>First</floor>
        <desc>A single desk with papers strew across it sits in the middle of the room.  A single desk lamp illuminates
the room, casting erie shadows into the corners. Out of the corner of your eye you swear something moved, but
but nothing else living appears to be with you.  The entry hall opens to the NORTH, and to the WEST a room lined
with bookshelves opens, lit by sconces along the walls.</desc>
        <roomExits type="array">
            <exit dir="0">hall</exit>
            <exit dir="1"></exit>
            <exit dir="2"></exit>
            <exit dir="3">library</exit>
            <exit dir="4"></exit>
            <exit dir="5"></exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomItems type="array">
            <item>Pantry Key</item>
        </roomItems>
    </room>
    <room id="library">
        <roomName>Library</roomName>
        <floor>First</floor>
        <desc>Book shelves line the walls, lit by three sconces along the NORTH, SOUTH, and EAST walls. The NORTH sconce
flickers incessantly, it seems to be hanging slightly askew. To the EAST a single lit desk sits alone in a room.</desc>
        <roomExits type="array">
            <exit dir="0"></exit>
            <exit dir="1"></exit>
            <exit dir="2">study</exit>
            <exit dir="3"></exit>
            <exit dir="4"></exit>
            <exit dir="5">dungeon</exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomItems type="array">
        </roomItems>
    </room>
    <room id="dungeon">
        <roomName>Dungeon</roomName>
        <floor>Basement</floor>
        <desc>A long subterranean hall leads EAST to a large iron door. On either side of the hall, several cells are barred
by rusted iron gates, manacles chained to the wall. </desc>
        <roomExits type="array">
            <exit dir="0"></exit>
            <exit dir="1"></exit>
            <exit dir="2">sacrificialChamber</exit>
            <exit dir="3"></exit>
            <exit dir="4"></exit>
            <exit dir="5"></exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomItems type="array">
        </roomItems>
    </room>
    <room id="sacrificialChamber">
        <roomName>Sacrificial Chamber</roomName>
        <floor>Basement</floor>
        <desc>A macabre scene lies before you. A blood drenched altar sits in the center of the room, surrounded by seven
lit candles. Bodies lie in the corner of the room, mouths agape in horror, no... wait... those are CPR dummies. There
does not appear to be another exit from this room other than the door to the WEST you entered from.</desc>
        <roomExits type="array">
            <exit dir="0"></exit>
            <exit dir="1"></exit>
            <exit dir="2"></exit>
            <exit dir="3">dungeon</exit>
            <exit dir="4"></exit>
            <exit dir="5"></exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomItems type="array">
            <item>CPR Dummy</item>
        </roomItems>
    </room>
    <room id="upstairsLanding">
        <roomName>Upstairs Landing</roomName>
        <floor>Second</floor>
        <desc>A small landing at the top of the stairs emerges from the darkness. Closed doors to the NORTH, EAST and
WEST beg to be opened. A string dangles from the ceiling, indicating something might lie in the attic UP.</desc>
        <roomExits type="array">
            <exit dir="0">nursery</exit>
            <exit dir="1"></exit>
            <exit dir="2">masterBedroom</exit>
            <exit dir="3">guestBedroom</exit>
            <exit dir="4">attic</exit>
            <exit dir="5">hall</exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomItems type="array">
        </roomItems>
    </room>
    <room id="nursery">
        <roomName>Nursery</roomName>
        <floor>Second</floor>
        <desc>A baby's bedroom opens before you, the crib knocked onto its side. A rocking chair, seeming moving on its
own, slowly creaks back and forth in the corner. A child's toys lay strewn about the floor. The only exit
is the SOUTH door you came through.</desc>
        <roomExits type="array">
            <exit dir="0"></exit>
            <exit dir="1">upstairsLanding</exit>
            <exit dir="2"></exit>
            <exit dir="3"></exit>
            <exit dir="4"></exit>
            <exit dir="5"></exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomItems type="array">
            <item>Baby's Rattle</item>
        </roomItems>
    </room>
    <room id="masterBedroom">
        <roomName>Master Bedroom</roomName>
        <floor>Second</floor>
        <desc>The door opens to reveal a luxurious bedroom, impeccably kept. Not a speck of dust is in sight. A
phonograph is playing Louis Armstrong's "What a Wonderful World" softly by the bedside. Several silver keys lie
on the bedside table. The only exit is the WEST door you entered through.</desc>
        <roomExits type="array">
            <exit dir="0"></exit>
            <exit dir="1"></exit>
            <exit dir="2"></exit>
            <exit dir="3">upstairsLanding</exit>
            <exit dir="4"></exit>
            <exit dir="5"></exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomItems type="array">
            <item>Study Key</item>
        </roomItems>
    </room>
    <room id="guestRoom">
        <roomName>Guest Room</roomName>
        <floor>Second</floor>
        <desc>You enter a modest bedroom, old stained family photos line the walls. There is a slight mildew smell, as
there appears to be water damage on WEST wall. On closer inspection, black sludge slowly oozes down the wall
from the ceiling. The only exit from this room is the EAST door you entered through.</desc>
        <roomExits type="array">
            <exit dir="0"></exit>
            <exit dir="1"></exit>
            <exit dir="2">upstairsLanding</exit>
            <exit dir="3"></exit>
            <exit dir="4"></exit>
            <exit dir="5"></exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomItems type="array">
        </roomItems>
    </room>
    <room id="attic">
        <roomName>Attic</roomName>
        <floor>Third</floor>
        <desc>Someone shouts "Hey, get out of here!" as you climb the stairs into the attic. It seems you accidentally
entered the control center for the haunted house. A man dressed in a cheap vampire costume hunches over a CCTV
monitor while another person, the one who yelled at you, handles several radios.  You should probably go back DOWN.</desc>
        <roomExits type="array">
            <exit dir="0"></exit>
            <exit dir="1"></exit>
            <exit dir="2"></exit>
            <exit dir="3"></exit>
            <exit dir="4"></exit>
            <exit dir="5">upstairsLanding</exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomItems type="array">
        </roomItems>
    </room>
</house>